

# Andrii Nizinkovskyi

andrii.nizinkovskyi@gmail.com

+38067 40 570 40

https://ua.linkedin.com/in/andriin

andrii.nizinkovskyi 🏼 🕄

#### **Objective**

Quick-witted, dedicated RubyOnRails developer seeking a full-time, permanent position with a company that will utilize and further enhance my knowledge of IT, and offer advancement opportunity

## **Summary**

A highly resourceful, innovative, and competent Web developer with extensive experience in design and coding of projects.

Possessing considerable knowledge of the development of applications, using programming languages and databases.

Experienced in developing applications and solutions for a wide range of study and public sector clients and having the enthusiasm and ambition to complete projects to the highest standard

# **Web Developer** 2015-present

Responsible for working on a range of projects, designing appealing websites and interacting on a daily basis with clients.

- Developing and maintaining the front/back -end functionality of websites;
- Participating in discussions with clients to clarify what they want;
- Providing technical support to end users;
- Designing prototypes for websites;
- Creating logos, UI elements;
- Writing cross-browser compliant HTML, CSS & JavaScript;
- Identifying and correcting existing web application;
- Deploying projects to VPS.

## **Work History**

# **Teacher in IT Academy**08.2016-present

Breaking down even the most abstract development concepts into concrete skills and can imagine fun examples to show learners all the way of Web.

- Identify the skills necessary to become an entry-level Frontend developer;
- Design a Frontend learning path consisting of individual courses and projects;
- Write the content of courses within the Frontend

learning path;

- Write and produce screencasts;
- Design projects that test students' acquisitions of required skills;

Collaborate with experts as necessary for certain courses

# **Chief Specialist** 2011 – 2015

Implementing and administering data loss prevention software.

Providing privacy policy.

Developing safety systems according to computer system evaluation criteria of Ukraine.

Creating and managing video IPTV/CCTV, security alarm and access control systems.

Managed of 14 subordinates.

Officer of the Department Regime, Security and Information Protection at the State-Owned Science-Industrial Association "Fort" of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine (firearms and special equipment for army and law enforcements)

#### Senior Engineer 2008-2011

Creation and administration of complex systems of limited access for processing government information with limited access.

Officer of the Department of Technical Information Protection at the Main Department of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine of Ukraine in the Vinnytsia Region.

### IT Academy

Vinnitsa, Ukraine 2014 – 2015

#### Studied programming

#### Education

#### Kharkov National University of Internal Affairs 2004 – 2008

#### Bachelor of informational security

- Time management
- Ability for efficient problem solving
- Goals orientated
- Ability to handle stress and work in multi-tasking situations
- Teamwork
- Ability to multi-task, react quickly to shifting priorities
- Continuously monitoring industry trends, technologies and standards

## Functional Skill Set

- Able to clearly communicate technical data to non-technical colleagues and clients
- Possessing all-round analysis and programming skills

| Languages          | [ Ruby, PHP, JavaScript, XML, HTML/HAML, CSS/SASS, C++, C#, QML ] |
|--------------------|---|
| Libraries/kits     | [ JQuery, D3.js, Chart JS, Leaflet, Momemt.Js,                    |
|                    | Xeditable, Summernote/ckeditor, MDB,                              |
|                    | Bootstrap, Font Awesome, Imagemagick,                             |
|                    | QT SDK, Android SDK ]   |
| Technologies       | [ AJAX, RESTful ]   |
| Databases          | [ MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL ]                                    |
| Frameworks         | [ Rails, Laravel ]  |
| CMS implementation | [ WordPress, OpenCart, Joomla, Drupal ]                           |
| Graphics software  | [ Photoshop, Illustrator, CorelDraw ]                             |
| OS                 | [ Windows, Ubuntu, Fedora, CentOS ]                               |
| Development tools  | [ Putty, Git, Redmine, Jira, Trello ]                             |
| IDE's              | [ NetBeans, Qt Creator, Visual Studio,                            |
|                    | Android Studio, WEB/PhpStorm, RubyMine ]                          |
| Methodologies      | [OOP, MVC]  |
| SCM's              | [ GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab ]                                     |
| Other knowledge's  | [ Network technology's, Deploy, Agile, Heroku, AWS ]              |

Experience in development for Windows, Linux and MacOS platforms Experience the collective teamwork software development (design, build release, make installation packages, deploy app, testing)

## Technical Skill Set

GitLink: <a href="https://github.com/kavaleriy/budget">https://github.com/kavaleriy/budget</a> (public)

WebLink: https://openbudget.in.ua/

Process time: 07.2016 - till day

Project's language - Ruby, framework - Rails

The "Open Budget" is intended to create tools to increase transparency and accountability of local

authorities.

#### OpenBudget

Strategic objective is to spread the project to all instruments of cities of regional subordination Ukraine that have their own developments in the field of financial transparency and accountability.

Role and Contribution:

- Developing and maintaining the front/back -end functionality of websites;
- Creating new and correcting existing web application modules;
- Managing team of project;
- Deploying project to VPS;
- Redesign app interface;
- Refactoring old code

**Projects** 

GitLink: <a href="https://gitlab.com/enemy/budget2017">https://gitlab.com/enemy/budget2017</a> (private)

WebLink: http://budget2017.info/

Process time: 28.09.2016 - till day

Project's language - Ruby, framework - Rails

The "Budget2017" is designed to display infographics country budgets.

Budget2017

The goal of the project is that with the help of graphs and other visualizations show a difference in the country's budget over the years.

Role and Contribution:

- Developing and maintaining the front/back -end functionality of websites;
- Creating new web application modules;
- Creating visualization (chart's);
- Deploying project to VPS;
- Redesign app interface;

GitLink: https://gitlab.com/softgen.vn/CnC (private)

WebLink: http://bldng.info/

Process time: 15.07.2016 - till day

Project's language - Ruby, framework - Rails

The aim of our project - to provide local and associations of citizens online tool to control spending on utility bills and reduce consumption of gas, electricity and other resources.

Bldng.info

The authorities will be able to analyze the consumption of gas, water, electricity and heat in homes - and introduce energy efficient changes. Servicing companies and businesses - to offer their services to the insulation of buildings, installation of energy-saving or of other changes based on public data. And the people - to save on costs and keep pace with innovations by neighbors.

#### Role and Contribution:

- Deploying project to VPS;
- Managing team of project.

**GitLink:** https://gitlab.com/begemot.lery/opendata-dkan (private)

WebLink: http://opendata.rada.gov.ua/

Process time: 26.03.2016 – 21.07.2016

Project's language – PHP, CMS - Drupal

OpenData

The portal is designed to provide access to public information Verkhovna Rada of Ukraine in the form of open data and provides access to information on the possibility of its use next.

#### Role and Contribution:

- Developing and maintaining the front-end functionality of websites;
- Parse datasets from existing local source;
- Install project to VMWare;
- Redesign app interface;
- Managing modules.

GitLink: https://bitbucket.org/enemy\_vin/germes.git (private)

WebLink: http://germesonline.com/

Process time: 25.11.2015 - 27.12.2015

Project's language - Ruby, framework - Rails

Germes

Private personal static page app.

Role and Contribution:

- Developing and maintaining the front/back -end functionality of websites;
- Creating static pages;
- Deploying project to VPS

#### Student's project's. 01.2015 - 07.2015

GitLink: https://github.com/ITAAcademy/ITAInformator

IDE: Qt Creator OS: Windows/Linux

Project's language - C++

Role and Contribution:

ITAIn formator

Involved in developing settings (save settings in \*.ini file, parse settings file) and translation modules (on the fly);

Involved in developing currency functionality;

Fix bugs: conversion, about modules, etc.;

Redesign UI, build releases, made installation packages.

GitLink: https://github.com/ITAAcademy/OpenBoad/

IDE: Qt Creator OS: Windows

Project's language - C++

Role and Contribution:

Involved in developing settings module (save settings in \*.ini file, parse settings file);

OpenBoard

Involved in developing menu (animated buttons with functionality) and toolbar (with color piker) components;

Involved in developing parser functionality (parse input keys and display it's with OpenGL helps);
Involved in developing programs dialogs (font, color,

open, save).

GitLink: <a href="https://github.com/ITAAcademy/IntITA/">https://github.com/ITAAcademy/IntITA/</a>

IDE: PhpStorm OS: Windows/Linux

Project's language – PHP, use framework Yii.

*IntITA* Role and Contribution:

Involved in developing WYSIWYG-redactor (use

Imperavi redactor);

Create 2 plugins ("Save", "Close");

Create functionality "Load redactor" (load on click);

GitLink: <a href="https://github.com/enemy-vin/SEM/">https://github.com/enemy-vin/SEM/</a>

IDE: WebStorm OS: Windows/Linux

Project's language – HTML, JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap

Role and contribution:

Involved in developing one-page site to solve math

tasks;

Create 2 scripts to solve equations (quadratic, cubic);

#### Personal Details

Date of birth December 06, 1986

Family status Married, have daughter

Languages English, Russian, Ukrainian

# Hobbies and interests

Airsoft sport

SEM

- Table tennis
- Reading book's